<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Main page on ZwerOxotnik's UC</title><link>https://zweroxotnik.github.io/en/</link><description>Recent content in Main page on ZwerOxotnik's UC</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><atom:link href="https://zweroxotnik.github.io/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rules</title><link>https://zweroxotnik.github.io/en/discord/rules/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zweroxotnik.github.io/en/discord/rules/</guid><description>The server rules generally match the Discord guidelines by a principle: &amp;ldquo;the severity of a violation together with social behavior leads to appropriate punishment within the community&amp;rdquo;
The rules are short and subjective in social conflicts. Moderators keep order without inflated rights, although auto-moderation bot is enough in many cases. Just in case, contact with: ZwerOxotnik#7117
However, we cannot use &amp;ldquo;A Code of Conduct&amp;rdquo; to the full (For instance &amp;ldquo;Contributor Covenant&amp;rdquo; because of different goals of groups of people.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>https://zweroxotnik.github.io/en/discord/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zweroxotnik.github.io/en/discord/faq/</guid><description>Why I was been banned/kicked/muted? Most likely, you violated Discord guidelines или our Discord rules.
How I can be unbanned? You might argue the ban or prove there is no violation with ZwerOxotnik#7117 on Discord.
Is there another option for removing the penalty for a violation? There is a one, you must prepare and tell an informative lecture to our community on the ZwerOxotnik&amp;rsquo;s UC server without violations. Again, first, contact with ZwerOxotnik#7117 on Discord and your apply will be subjectively reviewed.</description></item><item><title>Commissions</title><link>https://zweroxotnik.github.io/en/arts/commissions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://zweroxotnik.github.io/en/arts/commissions/</guid><description>You probably expect something like this https://kiliankuro.carrd.co/, however, currently everything is individual, contact through Discord:ZwerOxotnik#7117 or zweroxotnik@gmail.com, if you want more privacy, please contact me through matrix: https://matrix.to/#/@zweroxotnik:matrix.org.
More on the previous page (You&amp;rsquo;ll find out details about types of my drawings, stylistics, examples, etc. there).</description></item></channel></rss>